Three strikers, three defenses that can't handle them. This card should be free.
We're starting with Ronaldo over one and a half shots on target. He's averaging almost
two a game over his last ten international starts and DR Congo foul for fun, which hands him the
set pieces and penalties to test that keeper all night. Fernandez and Leão are going to feed him
in the box non-stop, then water him in over a half a shot on target. He's Panama's main threat,
clearing this lately, and Croatia plays that high line and bleeds four and a half on target
a game. He only needs one counter to catch this, and we're capping it with Harry Kane anytime
score, seven of his last ten, and Ghana just shipped twelve on target with a backline in chaos.
He's on penalties and every set piece, so we're going to roll with that three leg parlay.
This one's almost guaranteed.